Yo, Marionette, you home?
>> Oh, for heaven's sake. It's a male.
What do you want, man? Say what you want
and go before I get my shotgun.
>> It's my birthday. I'm here to give you a
birthday invitation.
>> I don't want it.
>> You haven't even looked at it yet. Come
on. There's going to be cake and games.
You'll have a load of fun.
>> I don't need to. I have a strong
distrust of men. So whatever you're
offering, I don't want it.
>> Well, I tried. I'm only here because my
mom made me personally deliver it since
Twilight is married to your sister.
>> There, it's been delivered. Now get off
my property and never come near this
mobile home again, you pig.
>> Fine. You know what? Fine. I've got
better things to do than argue with a
huge [__] Guard, finish handing out
the invitations. I'm going home to
finish blowing up my bouncy castle.
>> Hey, guard. Since you serve the ponies
of Equestria, could you do me a little
favor? It's trash day. My dumpsters
around back. Could you bring it around
front?
>> I'm afraid I can't do that, ma'am.
Moving dumpsters isn't part of my
duties.
You're seriously going to make a little
lady like me do heavy labor? That's very
uncou of a man.
>> Well, when you put it that way,
>> I'm sure the princess would be thrilled
to hear about how you watched a helpless
woman perform manual labor.
>> Okay, fine. I'll get your damn dumpster
>> around back. Just don't go looking
through them. It's personal stuff.
Whoa.
I told you not to look.
This is from Shining Armor. This must be
his way of forgiving me for every cruel
things I've done to him.
>> How did you know that's from him? I
thought you couldn't read. I could smell
the dollar store power stick three in
one cool blue water body wash. Now go to
your rooms and find me something nice to
give him.
>> The hell you want us to get, [__] You
don't buy us jack [__]
>> Goodness, it's a scorcher today. And yet
still, the great and powerful Trixie
continues to prove herself the greatest
groundskeeper in all of Equestria.
>> Cool beans, toss me your pit sweat. What
was that?
>> I said toss me your sweat rag so I can
ring it out and get you a fresh one.
Seems nice being Princess Celestia's
personal lap dog. Not all of us get to
relax and drink lemonade on the
weekdays.
>> This isn't lemonade. It's actually
Sprite with yellow food coloring mixed
in. because I was too lazy to go to the
store.
Did you just roll your eyes at my
superiority? I saved Equestria eight
times. I think I've earned the right to
occasionally fake lemonade.
That's all.
Add up.
Why are you making random noises every
time I try to speak? It's a political
tactic to make vocal sounds while your
opponent is talking. They can't properly
get their point across if they're being
interrupted.
>> That's just being annoying.
>> Correct. That's why it works.
>> The point is, you have the easiest life
in Ponyville. God, this [__] looks so
chopped. Where does she get her hair
done? Everyone should be getting
straight bangs like mine because it
looks sexy. God, I hate this [__] I
wonder if she chooses to look like a
cheap hooker. Did she look in the mirror
with that hair and think she nailed it?
Because she didn't like, "No, [__] you
didn't nail shit." If anything, you lost
the hammer. I am so sick and tired of
this [__] being alive. It's no wonder
her inclusion was the beginning of the
end for My Little Pony. Generation 4.
>> Twilight, I'm done with the lawn.
>> Oh, wow. Aren't you special? No one
cares, [__]
>> Face it, sparkle. You wouldn't even
survive 1 hour in my horseshoes.
>> You want to bet? Actually, I do.
What? Why am I the color of Pinkie Pie?
I'm hideous. It's a new body swapping
spell I've been working on. I'll tell
you what, if you can spend the next hour
living my life, I'll admit I was wrong
and I'll buy you actual lemonade.
>> Oh, you're on. Cool. Here's directions
to Marionette's house. I want you to go
there and close all of the windows
quickly. Why? Oh my god. Will you hurry
up? You need to get there before it's
too late.
Dear God,
>> what's up?
>> I didn't know she lives on the south
side of Ponyville. This is the ghetto.
>> Welcome to the real world. Not every
pony gets to be Princess Celestia's
[__]
>> Which house is hers?
We had a fight last week, so it should
be the one with exactly three bullet
holes near the front door.
>> The doorbell is broken. I took a hammer
to it when she made me mad.
Damn, it smells like piss. Okay, now
close every window before piss fairies
get inside. I'm sorry. You know the
little fairy shits that fly through open
windows at night?
>> Starlight, have you been pissing in
Marionette's mobile trailer home? You've
just never been on the southside before.
Anyway, you'll hear them scratching at
the windows in about 20 minutes.
Marionette should be there in a bit with
the piss berry spray to help you ward
them off if she makes it home alive.
>> Oh, my onion rings are done. I'll call
you back later to see if you're still
alive.
>> Oh my god, I totally forgot to tell her
about my bro's birthday party.
>> Now, every pony, put your hands together
for the most spectacular prince the
Crystal Empire has to offer. My darling
son and husband to none other than
Princess Cadence, Prince Shining Armor.
>> Mommy, where is every pony?
>> What do you mean, Pumpkin?
>> I thought I told you to hire everyone in
Equestria. Why is it just the
princesses? Where are the strippers and
sexy hookers?
>> Well, I guess they were the only ones
who decided to come pumpkin.
>> God freaking damn it all. If I knew the
guest list would be this small, I would
have rented out a table at Applebee's.
This is the worst birthday ever. Tell
everyone to go home, Mom.
>> Shiny, you can't cancel your own
birthday.
>> That's why I want you to do it.
>> I'm not going to do that just because
you didn't get the amount of guests you
wanted. You're being a big baby.
>> I can if it's my birthday, you dirty
[__]
>> I'm here.
>> Thanks, Luna. But I was hoping for
someone who isn't legally obligated to
be here by royal decree.
>> Wait, you invited all of Equestria.
Yeah, and I already know what you're
getting at. That would be in the
millions. So, why' I just rent 110 by 10
ft bouncy castle? Well, that was going
to be exclusively for me. The rest of
you guys were just going to watch me
bounce.
>> This is pretty good.
>> The specimen appears to be distressed
eating despite being surrounded by
ladies. Perhaps he is gay.
>> I am not. I am angrily eating my cake
because my birthday has a 99% attendance
failure rate.
Luna, what are you doing? My wife and
asster are standing right there.
>> I wanted to see how you would react. I
thought it might be funny.
>> I hate goth chicks. You all smell like
pure unwashed ass. Maybe a birthday
present can turn this around.
A book
>> on constellations.
I thought you may find it to be quite an
interesting read.
Chrysalis, I don't know why you bother
to get me anything considering how much
I hate your guts. In fact, you're not
supposed to be within 2 miles of me. I'm
going to have a word with your parole
officer again.
>> Just open it. I'm sure you'll love it.
>> Dear God, Chrysalis, this this is this
is beautiful. Dare I say magnificent.
Where in the world did you find such a
wonderful thing?
Well, you're always complaining how
you're not allowed to say it.
>> Wow. Yeah, I guess I do that a lot, huh?
I didn't realize it until now, but you
really get me. This is incredibly
useful. Thank you, Chrysalis. Cadence,
can I talk with you in the hall for a
moment?
Cadence, when was the last time you got
me something like this?
>> Excuse me.
>> You heard me, woman.
>> I don't know. Maybe this castle you're
standing in. That doesn't count because
you live here, too.
>> Okay. Well, I bought you a waffle maker
>> that we both used one time and put in
the cupboard because we hated cleaning
it.
>> You know what? We aren't doing this
right now. We shall discuss this later.
>> And so, we shall. You don't touch my
birthday cake.
>> I'll go get that. You just keep enjoying
those onion rings.
Mom, sorry. Mom, sorry. Mommied, sorry.
My apologies for the intrusion. I was
hoping we might have a talk. Wa, she
looks just like Celestia.
>> I lived over 1,000 years ago, long
before modern Equestria. Several weeks
ago, you unleashed a spell that reversed
monstrous enchantments across a great
distance. Because I existed only as a
spirit, it restored me as well.
>> That part was admittedly not
intentional.
>> I am grateful nonetheless. But there is
another reason I came. A dear friend of
mine perished on that day. But she
cannot be laid to rest, for her soul is
trapped in the salt dimension.
>> I have no idea what's going on.
>> I am only a Pegasus. I possess no magic
to free her.
I know it's selfish of me to ask you of
this, but if you helped me.
>> Yeah, no thanks, but if you could come
back in an hour or so.
>> Sparkle, what are you saying? When
ponies are in trouble, saving them is
like your thing. It's like the one thing
you're good at besides throwing it back
when I demand.
>> Starlight, I brought the monthly piss
fairy spray.
>> Thanks. Why did you pull away from me
like that? I wasn't going to hit you.
>> Oh, yeah. Uh, I know.
What's that horrible buzzing sound?
>> Holy crap. The piss fairies are here.
Get behind the couch.
>> What took you so long, babe?
I was literally 2 seconds behind you.
Well, that explains it, [__] You
wanted to fly behind me so you could
check out my butt. What? No, that that's
not true. It's cool, [__] I already
know I got the fattest pair of buns in
all of Piss Fairy Village. I smell
something. I smell it, too. I think
there's some [__] hiding behind that
couch. Let me go kill them for you to
prove that I am loyal enough to be your
[__]
>> This is bad. If just one finds us, we're
surely dead. Are piss fairies really
that dangerous?
>> Pooky, you know, one piss fairy has the
magical power of 37 unicorns as the
Southid's apex predator. They're also
strictly homosexual. Get your spray
ready.
I found them. Come help me grab them
before they get away.
>> Jessica, baby, you you blew up my [__]
I'll kill you,
>> fool. You thought you could compete with
a piss fairy? How embarrassing. Oh well,
at least I'll have the satisfaction of
blowing your brains out, then pissing
all over your dead body.
>> Mary, turn on the ceiling fan. I'm going
to redecorate the walls with this little
shit's blood.
>> Hurry. Help me close the windows.
>> What are you doing?
>> Your hat was crooked, so I'm fixing it
for you.
>> What can you not? I don't like be
touched non-consensually.
>> How dare you use that tone with me? I
freaking own you.
>> Celestia, stop.
>> Silence. His body belongs to me, as does
your own. I will have sex with your
husband because I feel like it, and you
will pay me $50 as thank you money.
>> Yeah, he's just a man. Don't think he
has any rights.
>> Take his clothes away. He won't be
needing them where he's going.
>> Hey, give those back.
>> This is the Salt Dimension. Skywish's
heart must be around here somewhere.
Twilight. Might you have any ideas
where?
>> Look, I'mma be real with y'all. I don't
know jack [__]
Listen, some pony is riding up on
bicycles.
>> Never mind. They're just crippled.
>> One enters this domain without declaring
reason. What is your purpose?
>> We've come for Skywish's heart.
>> Skywishes, our evil overlord, is indeed
here. In fact, she is the overlord of
this dominion.
>> That's impossible. She couldn't be.
>> If you truly wish to meet her, then walk
the path. She rests in the castle beyond
towering salt formations.
>> We didn't come all this way to turn
around. Twilight, let's go. Do we fight
evil gods often? Can't we just like ask
Celestia to do it?
>> Sparkle first. You didn't finish your
onion rings. Now you're questioning
moral justice. You are being so weird
today.
This whole thing is stinky [__] I
only signed up because you said serving
sky wishes would make us powerful. Yeah,
why are we still stuck in these chairs?
Dare question our mechanical goddess.
But goddess, you keep saying she
appeared to you in a dream, but if
that's true, then how come she never
appeared before us? because you are not
worthy and your questioning of her
existence is proof of that. Skywish is
real and the moment those three are
finished dealing with her, I'll finish
dealing with them.
If them gone, who else is left to become
a god but me? We've lost it. Yeah, we're
calling the cops. Oh, I'm just the only
one who's not afraid to do what needs to
done.
Help me.
Where you think you going, [__]
Oh, there are no witnesses.
>> Well, there is one.
>> Oh, [__] My my queen.
>> I give you purpose. The privilege of
serving a god. Yet instead of seeing my
generosity as a gift, you use it as a
means to steal my throne.
>> Oh, I've always served you faithful.
I was the one that found your heart and
revealed you. No, I made you better. You
know what that means? I own you.
>> You made me this body, but inside it
rests my beating heart. Do not beseech
yourself a god, for I belong to no pony.
Your role was to keep others from
entering this domain.
>> Please have mercy.
>> I have no use for traitors. Your
punishment is to be trapped in this one
spot for all eternity, unable to move.
>> Hey, get this thing out of my wheel.
>> I'm leaving now.
Take back
Skye.
I've waited so long just to hold you
again. Please forgive me. If I had been
there, maybe you never would have become
this.
>> This is my punishment.
Twilight Sparkle, the pony which stole
my soul. Are you not satisfied with just
my essence? Must you steal my heart,
too?
Okay, Starlight, you win. Your life is
way harder than mine. I'll even buy you
lemonade.
Starlight, why is there a portal to the
salt dimension in my living room?
>> Aren't with her, are you?
>> With who?
>> Skywishes. An evil pony. She betrayed me
and captured your friends.
>> What? Where are they?
>> No, where she's keeping them. I can take
you to them if you take this spear out
of my wheelchair.
I'll hold on to this weapon for now.
It's useless in your hands because the
salt spirit doesn't work against
Skywishes, the goddess of salt.
>> Fight back, you idiot.
>> I am.
>> I mean, with your ridiculously strong
world shattering spells, you're casting
spells like a noob.
>> I'm still getting used to this body.
>> You're You're that girl who turned me
into a vampire. You let me go once.
You're not fully evil, are you?
>> You got it all wrong. I'm not Twilight.
My name is Starlight Glimmer. She traded
bodies. I didn't do [__]
>> Likely story.
>> The looks in her eyes have changed.
>> Yo, these [__] are crazy. I'm going
home.
Cooling systems engage.
It seems I lack the required data to
destroy a pony of your caliber. It would
make sense for me to withdraw and
coordinate a new course of action to
eradicate you.
Princess Celestia,
wait a minute. This ain't Celestia. Who
the heck is this [__]
>> She doesn't have much time.
>> What do you mean? What's happened to
her?
>> When Skywish's power renders a pony, the
salt spreads and only she can remove it.
>> Where did she go?
>> Beyond the salt wasteland is her sanctu.
It takes two weeks of non-stop travel to
reach the other side. And unfortunately,
there is no shortcut. That's why
Skywishes accepted me as an ally. This
chair is automated and never tires.
>> I'm going.
>> Fool. With all of us out in the air,
you'll be dead in a matter of days.
You'll never make it.
>> Miss Sparkle, I have to go. Sky wishes
had every opportunity to kill us all,
but she couldn't bring herself to do it.
She's still in there.
That settles it. We'll go together.
>> Look there. I'm pretty sure that's it.
>> Sky wishes will be waiting inside. I'll
take it from here.
>> We should go in together.
>> No, Miss Sparkle. You helped me a lot,
but this is something I need to do
alone.
>> Mine
and you made love to me that night.
I recognize
something
that time
couldn't erase.
You're getting quite tall. You know
that. It's starting to get difficult to
chase you around.
>> Even when I was small, you never could
keep up with me. You didn't do a lot of
things. And when you did, you would do
them wrong.
>> My role for you was supposed to be that
of a caring mother. But I also tried to
be your friend. I did my best, but my
old age kept me from being able to do
all the things that you could. And by
the time you grew up, I was already
dead. You had no other friends because I
stole all of your youth. That is
something I never should have done. But
we're both here now. We can begin again.
Begin again. And then what? You grow old
and die again? You catch some disease or
get into some stupid accident? Or you go
off and get married?
>> I don't have some terrible illness. And
aside from this partially fatal injury
you inflicted on me, I feel fine. And
I'm not exactly looking to get married
anytime soon. But you're right. Life is
like Jared Leto's acting career. You
never know what tomorrow will bring. But
you can almost guarantee it's going to
be [__] If that's what scares you, then
you can stay here in this place.
Please, Star. I still want to be friends
with you as well.
>> Star Catcher did it.
>> Crippled pony. How could you have done
this? cuz she is no longer worthy to the
goddess of salt. Salt dries up all
emotion and affection are proof of her
weakness. The only one who deserves to
be goddess here is me.
>> Oh my god, she's flying away.
The salt has forsaken me and it has
chosen her to be the new overlord.
>> Her name is Maple Syrup.
>> I am the exalted one.
When you come home every night,
you went and
you
will be holding tight.
What do you want from love?
We cried.
>> She blocked it with her bare hands.
was new. Every moment was
satisfied.
>> Out of Trixiey's way.
>> Hey, get back here.
>> Princess Luna, I have come to request
aid.
>> Never mind.
We had finally laughed until we cried.
But you never could be satisfied. We
have everything we have.
Finally,
>> it is done.
>> Not yet. Our fight is only beginning.
>> You downloaded my data. I downloaded the
required data to reach the same form you
did. The state of the abyss isn't
achieved through magical means, but
self-perception.
When a pony descends deeper into
themselves, that is how one enters the
abyssal state. I am the unfeilling
android forged from steel. The metallic
vampire who's lived for over 1,000 years
to consume the angel standing before it.
Just as she once consumed me centuries
ago.
I won't fight you because we are ponies
and all ponies should be friends and
friendship is magic. Heat. Heat.
Heat.
time we never really got
too.
>> Every pix you gather around to combine
your piss magic for an ultimate piss
magic blast attack.
>> Starlight is using one of her ultimate
techniques. She's taking an enormous
amount of magical energy and compressing
it inside her body to release like a big
ass fart.
You promise me that you will always
always be beside me. You promise me that
you will always always be around.
to say goodbye.
We never really got
and here I quite thought I'd be done
wasting away in medical care.
>> I'm sorry.
Oh, don't apologize. I suppose waking up
here is preferable to not waking at all.
>> I ended up forgetting who I was. I
forgot everything you tried to teach me
when I was small and I lost my way.
>> Sky wishes. Do you remember what you
always wanted?
>> I want to see the world. But that dream
is over. Our world is gone now.
>> But this is a new world and we can see
it together. Oh, Miss Sparkle. I'm
feeling quite better now. If you
wouldn't mind.
Sure.
That's much better.
Go on in.
Uh, hello. Trixie told me you two would
be here. I still don't really believe
it. I bought you both flowers. They're
plastic. I figured they'll last longer
that way.
>> Belle? Oh my. You've gotten bigger. I
think pretty soon you'll be taller than
me.
>> You remember me?
>> Truly, you're growing into such a
handsome young stallion.
>> Get away from me. I'll kill you,
[__] Shut up, [__] You don't get
to fret us when you pushed us off a
cliff. Tip her over. I'm done with this
[__]
>> Hey, Maple. It's a beautiful day. You
should head home.
>> I hate beautiful days.
>> Maple, can I ask you a question?
>> No.
>> Why did you want godly powers?
>> What do you think, [__] I'm stuck in a
chair. I don't have a cool disability
like autism. There are ponies with
things like autism. Do you know some
ponies even fake having it because it
makes them seem cool? Can you imagine
something pretending to me? Pretending
they can't walk.
>> No.
>> Exact. You know the circus came to town
last week. Do you know what that was
like for me?
>> Look, I came out here to talk, but if
you only want to trauma dump, I'll just
be on my way.
>> Everyone talks about the rides and games
and [__] I don't even go because most
rides don't even have ramps.
>> Oh my. You've fallen, haven't you? Let
me give you a hand.
>> No, I demand to be independent.
>> My some pony is grouchy today. Here,
have some pudding.
>> Mind if I park here? I don't own this
spot, [__] I hate carnivals, too.
They're always someplace with grass.
Yeah, wheels and soft ground don't get
along. Have you ever got stuck in the
mud before? Dozens of times. It's so
embarrassing when everyone rushes over
at once to help. Hey, would you like to
go to the river sometime? We can't. It's
surrounded by grass. I found another
path last year. It's longer, but it's
flat with hard dirt. there. There's
actual way. No one's ever told me. They
probably didn't know. So, one go. Yeah,
I'd like that.
I couldn't save Sky Wishes.
>> What are you saying? Of course you did.
>> No, I couldn't. Not on my own. I tried
talking to her at first, but nothing I
said mattered to her. She tried to kill
me, so I tried to kill her.
>> Sometimes it's fun to be bad, huh?
>> That's a terrible thing for a pony to
say.
>> Maybe, but I used to be bad, too,
remember? And then you taught me how to
be good. So, if you ever wanted, I could
teach you how to be bad.
>> What about Princess Celestia?
>> You spend so much time trying to appease
Celestia, and she doesn't even care. She
doesn't have to know. We can keep it a
secret.
All this time I've been trying to gain
Celestia's approval, but she just
ignores me again and again. Maybe I've
spent so long trying to be the perfect
little unicorn that I've forgotten what
it feels like to do something that I
want to do for a change.
And I really, really wanted to kill her.
It was quite a thrill if I'm being
honest. You know what, Trixie, you're
right. Maybe I'll see what it feels like
to be bad for a change.
This has got to be the dumbest
assignment Celestia ever put me on.
Like, there's no way Twilight would
steal chips from Dollar Tree at 2:00 in
the morning. She lives in an actual
tree. If she were hungry, she could eat
nuts and berries and other plant [__]
that fall from her ceiling.
Princess Luna
>> Shining Armor, you cannot continue. Turn
around.
>> Sorry, but I'm under strict orders to
personally arrest my sister and Trixie.
I've trained Trixie.
>> Oh, I get it. You're worried about how
I'll hurt your little apprentice.
>> She's not the one I'm worried about. I
know exactly how dangerous she has
become. Celestia has sent you on a
suicide mission because by killing you,
it would make Twilight appear as a large
enough threat to have the go-ahehead and
kill her.
>> Luna, you you do realize if you take
their side, I'm going to have to tell
Celestia. Please don't start this civil
war type [__] among the royals.
I know Celestia gave the order, but I'm
giving you a new one. Go home before you
get yourself killed. There comes a point
where blindly following authority
becomes foolishness. And if those two
have decided they want those Fritos,
they are getting those Fritos.
>> Twilight, where the hell you at?
>> Over here.
>> Princess Celestia was right.
>> You cannot change my mind, bro. I am
taking these chili cheese FTOs home with
me and I will not be paying for them
because I deserve free stuff for
constantly saving Ponyville.
>> You have changed.
>> No, I'm just taking control of my own
life.
>> Freedom is illegal in Ponyville, you
psychotic [__] I'm taking you to jail.
>> Try it, white boy. Trixie, now.
>> [__] She was hiding in the next aisle
over. I'm surrounded. Some pony help me.
Let go
>> now. Sparkle.
>> Victory is mine. Time to go back home
and finish off the rest of my birthday
cake.
Twilight. Why?
You are the only one that I could ever
dream about. I should have told you, but
I couldn't find a way. I couldn't make a
word come out. Now I think I'm losing
you. Can't you see I need you? Why you
me? You ever leave me? I can't imagine
life without you.
Now, let me hold you for just one more
night. I'll do anything.
Baby, don't you know
how I love you? Don't you know
do anything? I'll do anything.
Baby, don't you go